<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Swift on Accessibility -&gt; Up to 11!</title>
    <link>https://dadederk.github.io/tags/swift/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Swift on Accessibility -&gt; Up to 11!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dadederk.github.io/tags/swift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Traits of a good accessible iOS app</title>
      <link>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2021-01-21-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2021-01-21-01/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article was originally published in Medium
You may know that you can configure a UI component with an accessibility label. The accessibility label is the name of the component. You can also configure an accessibility trait. The accessibility trait is the role of the component, it gives the user information on how they can interact with it. When using VoiceOver, the trait is usually vocalised after the accessibility label.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessible iOS Apps: Up To 11!</title>
      <link>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2020-10-23-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2020-10-23-01/</guid>
      <description>My talk from #a11yTo Conf.
To celebrate, Apress is offering a 20% discount in my book &amp;ldquo;Developing Accessible iOS Apps&amp;rdquo; with the code &amp;lsquo;a11yTOConf&amp;rsquo; in their website. Valid till October 30, 2020.
Description: Let’s go on a journey to create, not just accessible iOS apps, but awesome accessible experiences that absolutely all your users will be able to use and love. How do we bring VoiceOver&amp;rsquo;s support to the next level?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for testing your iOS app’s accessibility</title>
      <link>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2020-08-11-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 18:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2020-08-11-01/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article was originally published in Medium
The cycle for creating great accessible apps starts and ends with testing. Sure, it is always better to get feedback from users to create an experience that holds up to their expectations. But that’s not always possible. Till you can do it, I think the way to go is to do your best. Build it as well as you can, then gather all the feedback you can get, apply the suggestions, test, repeat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving your App’s Accessibility with iOS 13</title>
      <link>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2020-05-13-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 18:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2020-05-13-01/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article was originally published in Medium
I know, iOS 13 has been with us for quite some time now, WWDC 2020 is just around the corner and we hope Apple will present again a ton of new accessibility features and improvements coming with iOS 14.
But it is almost Global Accessibility Awareness Day! And it is still a great time to catch up and implement everything new that was presented around accessibility in iOS 13 - it was a packed year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving your App’s Accessibility with iOS 11</title>
      <link>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2018-02-14-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 18:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dadederk.github.io/post/2018-02-14-01/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article was originally published in Medium
Apple introduced iOS 11 at their World Wide Developer Conference (WWDC) in June 2017. WWDC is Apple’s showcase of new tools and developer APIs covering iOS, macOS, watchOS, and tvOS. In this post we’d like to show you what’s new in accessibility in iOS 11, and how you can incorporate these features to make your app more accessible to your users.
If it is your first time reading about Accessibility in iOS, Apple has a pretty good definition for app accessibility:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>